(Transcribed by TurboScribe. Go Unlimited to remove this message.) Sam was known as the school bully.
He was tough.
He had a lot of muscles.
He was very tall, too.
He looked really scary.
He was mean.
He teased people.
He made fun of people's appearances.
He spent 10 minutes teasing one of his
classmates.
The classmate cried.
The classmate told the teacher.
The teacher talked to the bully.
The teacher called the bully's parents.
The bully's parents arrived at the school.
The bully, his parents, and the teachers all
talked.
The parents and the bully left the school.
The teacher gave an announcement.
The bully was kicked out of school.
He will never return.